# **Joan Canals Ortiz**

Junior Full Stack Developer with several years of experience in the use of different types of databases, web technologies, and with extensive experience in object-oriented programming during my stay in the career of Computer Engineering.

# **Work History**

2019-01 PRIVATE TUTOR (COMPUTER AND SCIENCE SUBJECTS) - 2020-01

2020-06 SPORT CENTRE RECEPTION (CDTH)

- 2021-10

2022-06 JUNIOR FULL STACK INTERSHIP (ITNUBE CONSULTING

- 2023-07 S.L)

## **Education**

2014-09 Scientific Baccalaureate - 2016-06 Mare de Déu del Carme, Terrassa

**Computer Engineering (96 credits exceed)** 

UAB

2022-09 **Advanced Degree in Web Applications Development** 

- 2023-07 Nicolau Copérnic, Terrassa

# **Courses**

2023-06 **OPENWEBINARS' REACT INTERMEDIATE COURSE** 

2022-07 **UDEMY'S JAVA MASTER COURSE** 



# **Personal Info**

#### **Email**

jco98web@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/joancanalso rtiz/

### **Skills**

**Problem Solving** 

Teamwork with Scrum

Code Optimization

### **Software**

Javascript	****
PHP	****
Laravel	****
React	****
Java	****
SQL	****
MongoDB	****
Node.js	****

# Languages

HTML

CSS

Inglés	****
Catalán	****
Español	****

# Hobby/Interest

Apps creation